- 吸血鬼后裔前情提要  - 你能预测未来
Previously on Legacies... You're the oracle.
接下来会发生什么
What's coming next?
新英雄崛起
A new hero rises...
但是可以被金箭击落
but can be felled  by the golden arrow.
为父之罪找上了女儿
The sins of the father are visited upon the daughters.
- 我们在哪  - 监狱世界
Where are we? Prison world.
我猜阿莉莎·常
I'm guessing Alyssa Chang
想要给我上一课
wants to teach me a lesson.
- 一共有两名囚犯  - 你是凯·帕克
- There are two prisoners. - You're Kai Parker.
你就是个怪物  那个吸血鬼
You're a monster. That vampire,
她才是真正的怪物
she's the real monster.
她和她的密友统治着世界
She and her cronies run this  world.
她之前在我们学校
She used to go to my school.
我知道我得做点什么
I knew what I had to do.
我没想把你放到人间
I wasn't gonna unleash you into the world.
如果你能逃避我们的追捕
If you can survive being hunted
一天
for 24 hours,
那我就放了你女儿
I will let your daughter live.
当时间破碎
When time fractures,
黑暗笼罩
darkness overwhelms.
但我找到了出去的办法  我不希望你忘记了
I found my own way out of here. And I'd hate for you to forget
唯一能救你的东西
the only thing  that can save you.
别担心
Don't worry.
很快一切都会痛苦的揭晓了
It will all be painfully clear  soon enough.
他在这儿
He's here.
等下
Wait.
趴下
Stay down.
Stay down!
温蒂  我不想伤害你
Wendy, I don't want to hurt you.
洁德  他在屋子里
Jade, he's in the house!
啊哈  你被抓到了
Tag. You're it.
拜托  咱们别打架啊
Oh, come on. Let's not fight.
我不想浪费你的血
We don't want to waste any of that blood.
那一晚我关闭了我的人性
I shut off my humanity that night.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
乔茜
Josie.
你干了什么
What did you do?
我治好了她
I fixed her.
第2季   第13集
吸血鬼后裔
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
但是当箭穿过他  新英雄陨落
* But when the arrow finds him, a new hero dies *
新英雄崛起  他就会飞升
* A new hero rises, and he will take flight *
但是当箭穿过他  新英雄陨落
* But when the arrow finds him, a new hero dies *
翻 译  霸气小肥鹅
新英雄崛起
* A new hero rises *
他就会飞升
* And he will take flight *
但是当箭穿过他
* But when the arrow finds him *
翻 译 煎饼  Emma
新英雄陨落
* A new hero dies *
新英雄崛起
* A new hero rises... *
别说了
Stop saying that.
新英雄崛起
A new hero rises
但是可以被金箭击落
but can be felled  by the golden arrow.
翻 译 RossyGeng
兰顿
Landon.
翻 译  晁安
不  不
No, no.
霍普
Hope.
你和我没有区别
We're not alone.
特效：小螺号
校 对   小狐狸
特 效   麦 斯
这些都是什么
Oh, what's all this?
我睡不着  我一晚上没睡
I couldn't sleep. And I was just up all night
想弄明白我是怎么飞的
trying to figure out how I was able to fly.
或者说  漂浮
Or, you know, float.
- 你怎么这么作啊  - 我就是从车库上跳了下来
- Oh, my God. Tell me you didn't. - Oh, it's just
我想知道我到底能不能让自己
from the top of the garage. I had to see
再飞起来
if I could make myself do it again.
现在的研究理论显示
'Cause the current working theory
是我们接吻的时候出现的肾上腺素激增
is the spike of adrenaline when we kissed
导致我飞了起来  但是目前为止
caused something to happen, but so far, um...
嘿
Hey.
怎么了
What's wrong?
我昨晚做了个梦
I had a dream last night
你受了伤  我却无法救你
that you were hurt and I-I couldn't save you.
都是预言搞得鬼  对吧
It's the prophecy, right?
就因为我飘在了天上那么一次
Look, just because I hovered
不代表我就是那个崛起的英雄
off the ground once doesn't mean that I'm the hero who rises.
弄不好是韦德呢
It could be Wade, for all we know.
- 他才是长了翅膀的那位  - 不  多里安说
- He's the one with actual wings. - No, Dorian said
我们军火库里被偷的
that there is a golden arrow
东西里有一根金箭
in the inventory of our stolen arsenal.
如果只有那东西能够击杀狮身人面兽怎么办
What if it is the one thing that can kill a phoenix?
然后你就像超女一样冲进来拯救了一切
Then you'll Superwoman in and save the day,
你一直都这样
like you always do.
最近我就感觉我是个不称职的英雄
Except I'm pretty much failing as a hero lately.
我不知道该怎么让萨尔茨曼一家回来
I have no idea how to bring the Saltzmans back.
我知道你觉得自己必须修正这些
I know-- I know you feel like you have to fix this...
因为我就是需要  如果我不把他们弄回来
Because I do. If I don't bring them back,
就没人会了
no one else will.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
如果我能跟他们聊聊
If I could just talk to them,
- 萨尔茨曼博士会知道  - 不行
- Dr. Saltzman would know what to... - That's not an option.
你跟我说了灵体投射到
You told me that astral projection
监狱世界是危险的
into a prison world is dangerous.
听着  我知道
Look, I know
你觉得这都是你的问题
you feel like this is all on you,
但是你不是独自一人
but you're not alone.
你还有我呢
You have me.
我们可以弄清的
We'll figure it out.
一起做英雄  记得吗
Co-heroes, remember?
好吧
Fine.
但是在金箭被找到之前  我们一起做英雄的时候
But this co-hero is officially banned from flight attempt
你绝对不允许再尝试起飞了  好吗
until the golden arrow is found, okay?
我不会让自己陷入危险
No putting myself in danger.
那你也别灵体投射
No risky astral projection.
成交
Deal?
再说了  那金箭跟找到了也差不多
Besides, that golden arrow of yours is as good as found.
我们手下的精锐都在追查多里安
Dorian has some of our top men working on it.
快点  呆子  快把它点亮
Come on, nerd. Just turn the damn thing on already.
我在读说明书呢
I'm reading the instructions.
上面写着  如果它离与它一模一样的蛾子
Now, apparently, this thing glows when it gets close
很近的时候就会亮光
to the other identical moth,
军火库里
which was
被偷出来的东西里
somewhere in the arsenal stash
- 就有它  - 神奇的洛杰克
- that got stolen... - Magical LoJack.
我知道了  我们能走吗
Got it. Can we go?
别着急  狼人小队
Slow down there, Teen Wolf.
这项任务不是我们负责
You're not in charge of this mission.
- 那你是负责人吗  - 没人负责
Oh, and you are? No one is.
所以你别发号施令了
So stop giving orders.
听着  你到底想不想拿回我们的东西了
Look, you want to get our loot back or not?
我们这是在浪费时间
'Cause we're wasting time.
多里安的态度很明确
Actually, Dorian was very clear
这次任务就是让我们来侦查的
about this being a recon mission.
- 我们知道  - 行了  老师的走狗
- Yeah, we know. - Okay, teacher's pet.
你们干嘛突然那么毒舌
What's with the sudden toxicity?
看到没
See?
根本没那么复杂  密尔顿
It's not that complicated, Milton.
这边
This way.
- 密尔顿  - 是他自找的  老兄
- "Milton"? - He asking for it, bro.
这是什么吸血鬼狼人梗吗
Um, is this a-a vamp-wolf thing?
不是
No, it's...
什么也不是
Um, it's nothing.
走吧
Come on. W...
那是什么
Well, what?
你对洁德做了什么
What exactly did you do to Jade?
乔茜  回答我
Josie, talk to me.
丽兹就在这边  我能感受到她
Lizzie's this way. I can feel her.
你为何要打破沙漏
Why did you break the Sandclock?
我不记得了
I can't remember.
你还好吗
Well, are you okay?
你疼吗
I mean, are you in pain?
不
No.
我这辈子第一次  感觉一切都
For the first time in my life, everything feels...
很清晰
clear.
在那里
There.
丽兹
Lizzie.
没事的  亲爱的  轻点
It's okay, honey. Easy does it.
爸爸
Dad.
有点不对劲
Something's wrong.
我感觉我要疯了
It feels like my mind is breaking.
没事
It's okay.
轻点
Easy does it.
我们把你送进医院
We need to get you to the hospital.
一切都会没事的
Everything's gonna be just fine.
爸爸  我喝了吸血鬼的血
Dad, I drank vampire blood.
求求你别让我死
Please don't let me die.
你不会死的
You're not gonna die.
好了
All right.
有什么可以帮你的吗
Can I help you?
哈喽
Hello.
我叫约书亚
My name's Joshua.
阿拉里克说我要是来城里了可以来他这里
Alaric said I could drop by and stay for a few days
住几天
whenever I'm in town, so...
所以我就来喽
here I am.
你怎么认识萨尔茨曼的
How-how do you know Dr. Saltzman?
里克和我是老相识了
Oh, Ric and I go way back.
我还参加了他的婚礼
I was at his wedding.
还送了他一份特别的礼物呢
Brought quite the gift.
是嘛
Yeah.
很抱歉  他现在不在
I'm sorry. He's not here.
不过  等他回来了我会告诉他你来过的
Yeah, I'll-I'll let him know that you stopped by, though.
不  就算你告诉他也没意义了  他应该忘记我了
No, there's no point. He wouldn't remember me.
我听说学校最近挺忙的
But I hear it's been a little hectic at the school lately,
你应该不会像往常一样按时服用马鞭草了吧
and you might not have taken your vervain as usual.
你应该去
Why don't you go
找一个可以邀请我进来的人
find someone who would be able
过来
to invite me in.
你会没事的  丽兹  没事的  没事的
You're gonna be okay, Lizzie. It's all right, it's all right.
黑魔法让她现在的情况变得更糟了
The black magic is making her worse.
- 黑魔法在她体内的话她是撑不过去的  - 好吧  乔茜
- She won't make it with it inside her. - Well, Josie,
你可以做点什么吗
can you do something?
乔茜  拜托了
Josie. Please.
我要昏迷一会儿
I'll be unconscious for a little while.
别被吓着了
Don't be scared.
我能帮你
I can help.
萨尔茨曼博士
Dr. Saltzman.
是我
It's me.
我也不知道怎么回事
I don't know how,
但乔茜让我恢复了人性
but Josie turned my humanity back on.
听着  如果想的话你仍然可以杀了我  好吗
Look, you can still kill me if you want to, all right?
我知道这是我罪有应得
I know that I deserve it.
但我十六岁的时候参加过急救员的培训
But I was training as an EMT when I was 16,
而且过去的十年我也一直在
and I've spent the last ten years learning
别人打架后学着如何处理伤口  行吗
how to patch people up after a fight, all right?
我能帮她
I can help her.
但我无法离血太近
But I can't be near the blood.
所以你可以按我说的做
So you're just gonna have to do exactly what I tell you.
嘿
Hey.
这都是什么
What's all this?
一个不会飞的英雄还是有用的
A flightless co-hero being useful.
- 有进展了嘛  - 没有
- Any progress? - No.
阿莉莎施了咒语  所以每次修理它
Alyssa spelled it so every time I repair it,
它都会再次断裂
it just breaks again.
你没办法清除
And you can't...
咒语吗
unspell it?
没办法
No.
不  一定是我忽略了
No. There's got to be
什么地方
something I'm overlooking.
在这儿啊
There is.
抱歉打扰一下  你是星盘找错了吧
Sorry, you have the wrong ascendant.
谁说的
Oh? Says who?
伙伴们  这是
Fam, meet...
- 约书亚  - 哈喽
- Joshua. - Hello.
里克的老朋友
Old friend of Ric's.
热烈欢迎
And-- drumroll, please--
有关监狱世界的事情
he's also an expert
他也是个行家
on prison worlds.
我跟他讲了我们的困扰
I told him about our problem.
你介意我
Do you mind if I...?
非常感谢
Thank you so much.
成了碎片了
It is in pieces.
我的天
Oh, my.
嗯
Yeah.
这上面有个连接咒
There's a linking spell on this.
它发出了一种微弱的嗡嗡声
It produces a, a faint hum,
就像  就像是一种旋律  你
like a, like a melody, if you,
如果你知道该去听什么的话
if you know what to listen for.
很显然你不知道
You clearly don't.
当萨尔茨曼家族的人在这个星盘上
When the Saltzmans performed
施展魔法的时候
their spell on-on this ascendant,
他们自己也就被绑在了另一个星盘上
they were being tied to another.
拿好
Hold this.
你们的那个女巫
That witch of yours
没有把他们送到  你知道的
didn't send them to, you know,
那个新的空的监狱世界
a new, empty prison world.
她把他们送到了一个古老的
She sent them somewhere, somewhere
暗藏危险的
far older and...
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
监狱世界里去了
...much more dangerous.
要想救他们出来
And you're going to need my help
你们需要我的帮助
to get them out.
你们这些混蛋能听我的吗
Would you asshats listen to me?
我们得走这边
We got to go this way.
你是说这边吗  麦哲伦
You mean this way, Magellan.
干得漂亮
Nice job.
- 你弄坏了  - 不是我弄坏的
- You broke it. - I didn't break it.
伙计们  听着  我觉得我们应该停下来休息五分钟
Guys, listen, I think we should just take five
- 仔细看看指令  - 拜托  拜托
- and read the instructions. - Oh, please, please.
- 我们可能错过了  - 别告诉我
- We might have missed... Spare us your
说你有进化了的吸血鬼的五感
"I'm an evolved vampire" act.
嘿  离他远点
Hey, leave him alone.
不然怎样  你打算念叨到我死吗
Or, what, you'll sing me to death?
伙计们  我  伙计们
Boy, I'll... Guys!
听着  不管以前的
Listen. It doesn't matter
吸血鬼和狼人之间有多深的
what the previous generations of werewolves and vampires
- 仇恨  - MG
- did to each other. - MG...
而我有一部分朋友
Some of my best friends
- 也是狼人  明白吗  - 听着  米尔顿
- are wolves, okay? - Look, Milton, it's...
我们必须抛开那些偏见
We have to rise above the stereotypes.
- 我们得  - 是阿莉莎
- We have to abso... - It's Alyssa.
谁
Huh? Who? Wha...?
你这些混账行为
You're acting like a dick
就是因为我和阿莉莎约过一次会吗
because me and Alyssa had that
我是说  伙计
one date? I mean, it was a sting
那就是一个圈套啊
operation, man, and she straight-up
而且她把萨尔茨曼一家送去了监狱世界
sent the Saltzmans to a prison world.
据说的而已
Allegedly.
好吧  再说底线问题
Okay, bottom line,
腹黑邪恶的美女
dark evil temptresses
也不是我的菜啊
aren't really my thing anymore.
嗯  那她怎么老提到你
Yeah, then why are you all she ever talks about?
她眼里甚至都看不到别人
She doesn't even see the rest of us.
你是在指自己呢吧  兄弟
Uh, speak for yourself, homeboy.
你们俩都喜欢她
You're both into her?
这么说你们喜欢上了同一个人
So, y'all are into the same girl.
而她
And then she...
喜欢我
she's into me. Oh!
我想我肯定比你俩更讨人喜欢吧
I-I guess I must be cute or something.
趁你还能享受的时候尽情享受吧  因为我很确定
You enjoy that while you can, because I'm pretty sure
她肯定很快就会改观了
she'll be seeing things a little differently soon, so...
当然了  他们说一个人的视力好是首要的  所以
Yeah, well, they say eyesight's the first thing to go, so...
这样啊  那不然我现在把你弄瞎怎么样
Well, how about I mess up your eyesight right now?
闭嘴  看那里
Shut up and look.
我们追踪的目标会动
We're tracking a moving target.
比我们想象的还要糟
It's worse than we thought.
萨尔茨曼一家和杀了他们母亲的那个家伙
The Saltzmans are stuck inside of a prison world with
关在了一个监狱里  他们有危险了
the guy who murdered their mother-- they're all in danger.
阿莉莎一定把原来的星位藏起来了
Alyssa must have kept the original ascendant hidden.
你知道的  她不会轻易交出来的
You know she's not just gonna hand it over.
我必须得确认萨尔茨曼一家是否还活着
I have to know if the Saltzmans are still alive.
唯一的办法就是把灵体投射过去
And the only way to do it is to astral-project there.
霍普  我们约定过的  你可能会迷失在那里
Hope... we had a deal. You might get lost
- 找不到回来的路  - 我的梦里
- and not find your way back. - In my dream
乔茜跟我说  我们并不孤单
Josie said to me, "We're not alone."
- 好了  - 听着  兰登  我必须得试试
- Okay. - Look, Landon, I have to try.
如果因为我找不到救他们出来的办法  使他们一直处于危险中
If they've been in danger this whole time and something happens
出了什么事情的话
because I couldn't find a way to save them...
嘿  抱歉打扰了
Hey, sorry to intrude.
有好消息
Got some good news-- so...
约书亚一直在帮我们做研究  他说
Joshua's doing some research for us. He said there's
瀑布附近有一种稀有的花
a rare flower that grows near the falls.
它的成分会让人们说出他们内心深处的秘密
The extract makes people tell you their deepest secrets.
如果我们把这种花给阿莉莎
If we give that to Alyssa,
我们就能让她告诉我们星盘在哪了
we can get her to tell us where the ascendant is.
兰登  你和我来
Landon, you come with me.
- 好的  - 不行
- Yeah. - No.
他得留这儿
He stays here.
你试着联系下他们  我马上回来
You try to contact them, I'll be right back.
好吗
Okay?
如果有风险
If we take risks,
我们就一起承担
we take them together.
我会保证他的安全的
I'll keep him safe.
我答应你
I promise.
好的  你现在得止血
Okay, now you're gonna need to stop the bleeding.
托盘上有止血钳
There's a Laughlin clamp on the tray.
- 它看起来有点像  - 嗯  我知道它长啥样
- It kind of looks like... - Yeah, I know what it looks like.
是她妈妈发明的
Her mom invented it.
好的
Okay.
血止住了
Vessel's sealed.
她脉搏也稳定了
Her pulse is steady.
谢谢你
Thank you.
又见到你了
Hello again.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
她用黑魔法做了些危险的事
She did something dangerous with black magic.
而现在她也记不起为什么要那么做了
And now she can't recall why.
我一定有我的原因
I must have had a reason.
不过  我还记不起来
But it's blank.
有些片段从我记忆里流失了
There's something's missing from my memory.
或是有些人
Or someone.
我也一样
Uh... same.
我不知道这是什么  但我在口袋里找到的
I don't know what this is, but I found it in my pocket.
感谢你给我带来的这段性爱体验
——凯
凯是谁
Who's Kai?
那个从我们记忆中
The person who's missing
消失的人
from our memory.
有个魔咒在扰乱我的心智
There's a spell affecting my mind.
我以前也感觉到过
I've felt it before.
是马里之洼
Malivore.
你可能需要把椅子  洁德
You might want to grab a seat, Jade.
- 为什么  - 相信我
- Why? - Trust me.
咒语
Harae-tamai kioku  yomigaerashi-tamae.
著名的塞尔瓦托学院啊
The Salvatore School.
我怎么从没想到过你
How I've not missed you.
我跟你说过我一定能进来的
I told you I could get in.
重要的是  他们还提供蜜汁火腿
And they have honey ham.
别在这自吹自擂  真不好看
Don't brag-- it's unbecoming.
你低估了那个能给你带来威胁的三重混血儿
You underestimate the Tribrid at your own peril.
对付她  我有我的打算
Oh, I have a plan for her.
我总有自己的打算
I always have a plan.
那又是什么
Which is what?
如今  我把你要的信息都给你了
Now, I gave you all the information you needed,
因此  我觉得也是时候轮到你报答我了吧  异教徒
so now I think it's time you return the favor, heretic.
听着  亡灵巫师先生
Look, Mr. Necromancer.
是大名鼎鼎的亡灵巫师
The Necromancer!
绝无仅有的
The.
当然如此  你会得到你想要的  行吗
Sure. You're gonna get what you want, okay?
乔茜·萨尔茨曼  她浑身充斥着你想要的黑魔法
Josie Saltzman, crackling with all the black magic you need,
只要你走开  然后按我说的做
if you back off and do exactly as I say.
我听着呢
I'm listening.
那金箭还在你那吗
Still got that golden arrow?
应该不会花太久
This shouldn't take long.
对吧  我不敢相信我在神秘瀑布镇住了这么久
Right? I can't believe I've lived in Mystic Falls this long,
却从没真正地看到过瀑布
and I've never actually seen the falls, you know?
威廉姆斯先生
Mr. Williams?
你还好吧
You okay?
你肯定就是阿莉莎了
You must be Alyssa.
我是你伟大杰作的超级粉丝
Big fan of your work.
你觉得我们联手怎么样
How do you feel about team-ups?
丽兹在哪
Where's Lizzie?
楼上睡觉
Sleeping upstairs.
凯
Kai.
努力控制下你的情绪
Try to control your emotions.
我记得凯说过
I remember what Kai said.
我们还有办法出去
There's still a way for us to get out.
这个地方不过也就是另一个魔咒
This whole place is just another spell.
是魔法形成的
It's made of magic.
而魔法是可以被吸收的
Magic can be siphoned.
我可以在这个世界制造缺口
I can make holes in this world.
许多门
Doors.
那这意味着你能把我们带回现实世界吗
So, does this mean you can get us back into the real world?
没事的
It's all right.
我跟他们谈过了
I talked to them.
我们只是想回家而已
We just want to go home.
我们不能都离开
Well, we can't all go.
我在这儿吸收的魔法不能穿越到现实世界
The magic I siphon here can't travel to the real world.
能量必须有去处  也就是说
The energy needs to go somewhere, which means
得有人留下
someone needs to stay behind
来充当那个锚
to be the anchor.
应该让迭戈留下
It should be Diego.
无意冒犯
No offense.
不
No.
我们不能把任何人留在这
We're not leaving anyone here.
我们都得回去
We're all getting back.
有人来了
Someone's coming.
乔茜
Josie?
你好啊
Hello.
只有我看得到你
Only I can see you.
你怎么了
What happened to you?
我打破了沙漏
I broke the Sandclock.
天呐  真糟糕
Oh, my God, I'm so sorry.
亲爱的  你在跟谁说话
Honey, who are you talking to?
霍普  她正在施灵体投射术
Hope-- she's astral-projecting.
听着  你得警告她小心凯
Listen, you have to warn her about Kai.
为什么  发生了什么
Why? What happened?
凯走进了马里之洼  我们认为
Kai went into the Malivore pit, and we think
他正试着去往现实世界
he's trying to get to the real world.
实际上  我认为他已经在这了
Actually, I think he's already here,
冒充了其他人
pretending to be someone else.
凯在学校
Kai's at the school.
霍普
Oh. Hope?
听我说  凯十分危险
Listen to me, Kai's incredibly dangerous.
你现在得让他立刻离开学校
You have to get him away from the school now.
祝你好运  霍普
Good luck, Hope.
等等
Wait...
我们得不惜一切代价离开这
We need to do whatever it takes to get out of here.
好吧
Fine.
我们施咒吧
We do the spell.
我留下
And I'll stay behind.
你们都曾是我的学生
You were all my students once.
留下的必须是我
It has to be me.
刚那投射术进行得如何
How'd all that go?
不怎么样
It didn't.
我没有感应到他们
I couldn't reach them.
你是需要什么吗
Did you need something?
不是你的味道
It's not you.
也不是我的
It's not me.
你说什么
Excuse me?
不对
No.
对  找到了
Yes, there it is.
为什么总选毛绒玩具
Oh, why is it always stuffed animals?
这是最奇怪的
It's the weirdest thing.
你怎么知道的
How did you know?
阿莉莎·常只需要一个
Oh, Alyssa Chang just needed a, uh,
有同情心的人听她说话
a compassionate ear to bend.
我很抱歉
Hey, I'm sorry to, uh,
多管闲事了  但她真的很不喜欢你们这群人
stick my nose in, but she really doesn't like you people.
不管怎么样
Anyhoo...
现在你们需要的是
now all you need is something
一件拥有和一场天象同等能量的东西
that has the equivalent power of a celestial event.
有想法吗
Do you have any ideas?
当然
I do.
但我们得离开校园
But we have to go off-campus
去拿
to get it.
有谁不爱实地考察呢
Who doesn't love a field trip?
闻起来很旧了哈
That smells old.
这里看着不像是存有
This doesn't seem like much of a spot
强大魔法物件的地方啊
for a powerful magical artifact.
也不像有毛绒大象玩具的地方
Neither does a stuffed elephant.
那太好了
That's very good.
萨尔茨曼博士把我们要找的藏在其中一个箱子里  所以
Dr. Saltzman hid what we need in one of these crates, so...
就找带塞瓦托尔标志的
Look for the Salvatore logo.
幸好这里也就那么
It's a good thing there's not, like,
四百个箱子要找
400 crates in here.
找啊找啊
Eeny, meeny,
找箱子
miny, crate.
你说的塞瓦托尔标志  是那种
When you say Salvatore logo, you mean, like, that
带着S和花体字的那种吗
thing with the "S" and the squiggle?
这下开始了
And so it begins.
咒语
Icaeus.
不错嘛
Nice try.
你本可以阻挡的
You could have blocked that.
是  你说得对
Yeah, you're right.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
我只想让你觉得自己很厉害
I-I just wanted you to think you were doing a good job.
你不会想打我吧
You're not trying to beat me.
不不不  暂时不想打你
Oh, no. No, not for a... a few more minutes.
因为现在
Because right now,
阿莉莎·常正在施咒  咒语会切断
Alyssa Chang is performing a spell that will sever
我与监狱世界的联系
my connection to the prison world.
而那个世界是为我创造的
And since that place was created
只要她施咒了
for me, once she's done...
那个世界就会消失
The world will disappear.
其中的人也会随之消失
Along with everyone inside of it.
感谢你的恶人独白
Thanks so much for the villain monologue.
我之后再来收拾你
I'll deal with you later.
急着走之前
Hey, before you go rushing off,
有些事你该知道
there's something you should probably know.
我操控了那个家伙
I compelled what's-his-name.
就是那个
Who's with, uh,
跟你男友在一起  卷发的那个
you know, your boyfriend, curly-hair?
噢对  你男友兰多
Lando. There it is.
多亏了你
That's thanks to you.
我们在此聊天之际
As we sit here chatting,
他们正往东去  出了学校
they're headed east, away from the school,
进入了森林  径直进入
into the woods, walking straight into the path
金箭之路
of a golden arrow.
你骗人
You're lying.
但这次没有
You know, for once, I'm not.
我们可以见识一下  那个预言是不是真的了
I guess we'll find out if that prophecy's really true.
你脑子里就别算计了
Oh, you can stop doing the math in your head.
你不可能同时赶到两个地方去的
You'll never make it to both places in time.
你无法全救下来的
You can't save them all.
所以你有个小小的选择要去做了
So, you, uh... you have a little choice to make.
要救谁
Who's it gonna be?
- 这下谁是英雄啊  - 你认真的吗
- Now, who's the hero now? - Are you for real?
兄弟们  我听到有动静
Guys, I, I hear something.
但是你有帮手啊  正经出力的事都是我来的
But, man, at most, you get an assist. I did all the heavy hitting, for real.
你踢他的胸口  我刺他的
You kicked him in the chest. I stabbed him in the...
我用了吸血鬼的能力  杰德
I used my vampire powers, Jed.
是你像个小孩似的拿木棍刺了他
You're the one that hit him with a stick like a child.
我又快又强
I'm so damn fast and so strong...
拉斐
Raf?
天啊  怎么回事
Oh, my goodness. What happened?
没事的  兄弟
It's gonna be all right, man.
我们带你离开这
We're gonna get you out of here.
我们得齐心协力
We need to work together.
把杖尖围成一圈生成束缚咒
Place the spires in a circle to create a boundary spell.
我开始虹吸的时候
As I begin to siphon,
它们下面会有门打开
doors will open beneath them.
一扇门只能运送一个人
Each door can only transport one person.
只要我一开始施咒  直到完成我都无法停下
Once I begin the spell, I cannot stop until it is done.
所以你们看见门的时候  必须要走
So, when you see the door, you have to go.
爸爸  别这样  会有别的办法的
Dad, don't do this. We'll find another way.
丽兹  没时间了
Lizzie, there's no time.
凯出去了  他去了学校
Kai got out. He's at the school.
霍普想阻止他  但如果
Hope's trying to stop him, but if
阻止不成  你和乔茜就务必去阻止他
she can't, you and Josie have to.
你现在必须得走
You got to go now.
但是爸爸  赛巴斯提安还在这呢
But, Dad, Sebastian is still here.
- 他会找你的  - 我会没事的
- He'll come after you. - I'll be fine.
另外  你很快就会找到办法帮我回去的
Besides, you'll find a way to get me back in no time.
我很抱歉  我就不该
I'm so sorry. I never should have...
没事的  我爱你
It's okay. I love you.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
你没必要这样
You don't have to do this.
多里安住手  你不是这样的人
Dorian, stop. This isn't you.
我知道  但我停不下来
I know, but I can't stop.
那你一定是被操控了
Well, then you must have been compelled.
他们跟你说什么了
Wha-- what did they say to you?
他们到底让你干嘛
What exactly did they tell you to do?
我必须带你去石阵  在他们
I have to take you to the boulders and hold you
射出金箭的时候抓住你
while they shoot the golden arrow.
什么
What?
也许援兵就要来了
Maybe help is on the way.
你不可能同时赶到两个地方去的
You'll never make it to both places in time.
无法全救下来  你救哪个
You can't save them all.  Who's it gonna be?
不要
Don't!
你还真是个菜鸟女巫啊
You really are a basic witch.
阿莉莎  拜托
Alyssa, please.
我不想让他们回来  现在不想  永远不想
I don't want them back. Not now, not ever.
如果你施完这个咒  你就把他们都杀了
If you finish that spell, you'll kill them all.
他可没说过啊
He didn't say anything about that.
你想想
Well, think about it.
如果你切断连接  监狱世界就瓦解了
If you sever the connection, the prison world collapses.
里面的人都会死的
Everyone in it will die.
我知道你很生气
Look, I know that you're angry,
我也知道你想伤害他们
and I know that you want to hurt them.
但你不是个杀人凶手
But you're not a murderer.
相信我  你不想担上害死别人的罪责
Trust me, you don't want to be responsible for someone's death.
这种感觉会一直跟随着你
It stays with you.
你要永远承担着
You carry it forever.
我知道
I know.
这不是我弄得
That isn't me.
现在还不晚
It's not too late.
多里安  你可以战胜这个的
Dorian, you can fight this.
抱歉  兰登
I'm sorry, Landon.
我发誓过保护你安全的
I promised I'd keep you safe.
但他们射金箭的时候我必须抓住你
But I have to hold you while they shoot the arrow.
不得不这样  必须抓住你
I have to. I have to hold you.
你会没事的
You-You-You'll be okay.
我会去找帮手的
I'll go get help.
你会没事的
You'll be okay.
你不可能及时赶到的
You won't make it in time.
陪我呆一会儿吧
Just stay with me.
好的
Okay.
兰登
Landon?
没事的
It's all right.
不怪你  好吗
It's not your fault, all right?
无论发生什么  你依旧是位英雄
No matter what happens, you're still one of the heroes.
- 好的  - 听到了吗
- Okay. - You hear me?
无论怎样
No matter what.
好的
Okay.
不要  威廉姆斯先生
No. Mr. Williams?
我靠  管用了
Holy crap. It worked.
我会帮你出去的  我保证
I'll get you out, I promise.
我知道你会的
I know you will.
现在快走吧
Now you got to go!
我永远不会原谅你的
I will never forgive you.
就如同
It's like I was
你射杀我那晚我想对你说的一样
trying to tell you the night that you shot me.
有些人不懂得珍惜第二次机会
Some people don't know what to do with a second chance.
谢谢
Thank you.
我还让伊丽莎白陷入了危险
I put Elizabeth in danger.
如果你要谢我的话啊  就照顾好她吧
If you wish to thank me, take care of her.
我们到底要怎么样做
So, how exactly do we do this?
你触碰我  就会成为锚
You touch me and become the anchor.
好的
Okay. Um...
能告诉你姐姐
Can you tell your sister...
一位更优秀的男人会说的话吗
...something a better man would say?
你做到了
Hey, you made it.
乔茜
Josie?
是我啊
It's me, guys.
我回来了
I'm back.
兰登有麻烦了
Landon's in trouble.
怎么回事
What happened?
我不得不做选择
I had to make a choice.
还有
And...
我没选择兰登
I didn't choose Landon.
但没关系
But it's okay
因为他随时都会复活的
because he's gonna come out any second,
如果我
and-and if I...
当我睁开眼睛的时候
When I open my eyes,
他就会在那
he's gonna be there.
天那  我没看见他
My God. I don't see him.
我看见了
I do.
多里安  会没事的  兄弟
Dorian, hey, it's gonna be okay, buddy.
坚持下去  坚持住
Just hang in there, hang in there.
你能听见我吗
* Can you hear me? *
嘿
Hey.
丽兹这两天都不能活动
Lizzie should stay off her feet for a day or two.
而且她不能举重物
And, uh, she shouldn't lift anything heavy.
我
I'm, uh...
我很高兴真正的你回来了
I'm glad to have the real you back.
我也是
Same.
消失在黑暗中
* Fade to black *
你是去是留
* Are you coming or going? *
天堂可以等一等了
* Heaven can wait *
永恒太过久远
* Forever is too late *
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian.
永恒太过久远
* Forever is too late... *
我已经死了吗
Am I already dead?
这是灵体投射
It's astral projection.
乔茜在帮我
Josie's helping me. Ah.
我必须来看看你
I had to see you.
我们为了逃离这个世界
The spell that we did
施的咒语让这个世界不稳定了
to escape this world is making it unstable.
它快撑不住了
It won't last much longer.
正如他们所说  都是好结果啊
All good things, as they say.
呼唤着
* Calling... *
听着
Listen,
去乔治亚州的福特谷找一个建筑
go to a building called Triad Industries
叫三合会
in Fort Valley, Georgia.
那儿有个黑色的洞
There's a black pit there
那是去往另一个维度的门
that's a door to another dimension.
跳下去  你也许可以逃脱
Dive in, and maybe you can escape.
也许能吧
Maybe.
如果我及时赶到的话
If I make it in time.
消逝
* Fading, fade out... *
我很抱歉  我对你做了那些事情
I'm so sorry for what I did to you.
消逝
* Fade out... *
我也很抱歉  我选男人的品味太差了
I'm sorry that I have such terrible taste in men.
你知道  我们初遇时我是警告过你的
You know, I did warn you when we first met.
你本应该保持距离
You should have kept your distance.
消逝
* Fading, fade out... *
乔治亚州  福特谷
Fort Valley, Georgia.
说给我听
Say it back.
我记得呢
I remember.
这个世界呼唤着
* This world is calling... *
我会永远记着
I'll always remember.
苏醒着
* Awaken... *
再见了  伊丽莎白
Goodbye, Elizabeth.
消逝
* Fading *
消失了  困在两难之间
* Fade out, caught in the in-between *
消逝
* Fading, fade out... *
我想我会喜欢这个地方的
I think I would have liked this place.
消逝
* Fading, fade out *
困在两难之间
* Caught in the in-between *
消逝
* Fading, fade out *
苏醒了  我亲爱的
* Awaken, my darling. *
我记得的最后一件事
The last thing I remember
是从公交站台出来  然后
was coming from the bus stop, and then...
然后我
Then I-I...
我在拖车里醒过来  有个人
I woke up in that trailer, and there was someone in a...
穿着红袍子  我不知道
in a red robe. I don't know.
重要的是你现在安全了
The important thing is that you're safe.
我们以后会弄明白是怎么回事的
We'll figure out the rest later.
威廉姆斯先生
Is Mr. Williams
会没事吗
gonna be okay?
会的  他没事
Yeah. Yeah, he's fine.
他正在医院里以正常人的方式
He's healing the old-fashioned way.
养伤呢
In a hospital.
好了
All right.
现在情况是这样的
Now, here's the deal.
就破例这一次  好吧
This... is a onetime thing, all right?
我们这一天过得够呛  所以
We had a day. So...
致更美好的
here's to tomorrow
明天
being better.
- 致明天  - 会更美好
- Tomorrow. - Being a better day.
我真的以为我今天会失去你了
I really thought I lost you today.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你想念的真的是我吗
* Is it really me you're missing? *
你做了正确的选择
You did the right thing.
救六条命还是一条
Save six lives or save one.
谁愿意倾听呢
* Who'll listen? *
我知道对你来说  这样的损失会有多痛苦
I know how hard loss like this is for you.
期望越高 失望越大
* High hopes and low blows... *
你还是做出了正确的选择
You still made the right choice.
相信你会有多么痛苦
* Just how much it hurts to believe you... *
我不知道我真的能那么飞起来
I don't know that I could have done that.
但我需要你
* But I need you *
我应该克制
* I should help myself... *
因此你需要有担当
Which is why you need to be the hero.
你能做我们其他人做不到的事
You do what the rest of us can't.
但我无法克制了
* But I can't help myself *
这是真的我吗
* Is it really me... *
我可不会飞啊
Well, I can't fly.
还是只有我愿意倾听
* Or am I the only one who'll listen *
倾听你的话
* To you? *
如果我
* And if I... *
能告诉我飞的感觉是什么样吗
Will you tell me what it's like?
到了早晨一切会分崩离析吗
* Will it be pieces by the morning? *
就像超脱于地球之外
It's like falling away from the earth.
你所拨打的
* That you've tried? *
还是仅仅是另一个
* Or is it just another... *
我实在不会解释
I can't really explain it.
孤独的夜晚
* Lonely night... *
我只能什么时候带你上去
I guess I'll just have to take you up sometime
这样你就能自己体验了
so you can see for yourself.
因为我只会在你让我失望的时候
* 'Cause I only ever tell them *
向别人倾诉
* When you're letting me down *
你想念的真的是我吗
* Is it really me you're missing? *
还是只有我愿意倾听
* Or am I the only one who'll listen *
倾听你的话
* To you? *
如果我今晚接起电话
* And if I pick up the phone tonight *
到了早晨一切会分崩离析吗
* Will it be pieces by the morning? *
你只拨打了
* Am I the only number *
我这一个号码吗
* That you've tried? *
还是仅仅是
* Or is it just *
又一个孤独的晚上而已
* Another lonely night? *
你想念的真的是我吗
* Is it really me you're missing? *
真的是我吗
* Is it really me? *
凯·帕克  你这机灵的
Kai Parker, you brilliant,
灵活的
flexible...
太棒了
Yes.
真棒
Oh, good.
你还在啊
You're still up.
- 我一直都在  - 那就
- I'm always up. - Well, then,
派个仆人来把我放了
send a minion to free me.
这样你就能再骗我了
So you can lie to me again?
断开与你的联系
Severing your connection
会消灭我需要的黑巫师
would have killed the dark witch that I need.
背叛现在都算是常态了
Yeah, betrayal's sort of a habit at this point.
但如果你把我放了
But if you set me free...
黑巫师已经回来了
The dark witch has returned,
所以我不再需要你了
so I no longer need you.
我听到有人来了
And I hear someone coming.
鉴于我们以前的恩怨
Given all we've been through,
这有点虎头蛇尾啊
this feels a little anticlimactic.
你不觉得吗
Don't you think?
我可没有
Not to me.
这
This...
是为了乔
...is for Jo.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）